Guide to the Myron S. Falk Papers 1867-1950 MS 3047
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Financial and Legal Papers, 1905-1947; 1.96 Linear feet
  This series includes the financial and legal papers of Myron Falk and his family members, including his wife, Milly Falk, his father-in-law, Henry L. Einstein, and his children, Mildred, Eleanor and Myron Falk Jr. from 1898-1946. The series includes financial diaries, appraisals of his properties at 130 East 44th St and in Greenwich, Conn. (often referred to as Port Chester, N.Y.), and documents relating to estates, trusts, wills and testaments, tax documents, and insurance policies. A large portion of this series contains general financial and legal correspondence, bills, club dues, and account statements. Some correspondence relates to Falk's investment in the Mercury Theatre and a dispute with Orson Welles concerning use of the Mercury name outside of the Theatre's interests.
  Arranged in rough chronological order.
  - Financial diaries (4 folders), 1910-1945 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6-9)
  - Investment accounts diary, 1926-1930 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ledger books (2 folders), 1911-1935 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Ledger book. Flat box, 1917-1936 (Offsite-box 6)
  - Appraisal of 130 East 44th St, 1921 April (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
  - Inventory and Appraisal of Furnishings and Personal Effects of Myron S. Falk, King Street, Port Chester, N.Y., 1921, 1923 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
    Also contains bills and receipts from Japan dated 1923 for items possibly bought during the Silk Mission (artwork, sculptures, textiles, etc.).
  - Estate of Milly E. Falk (2 folders), 1916-1922, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15-16)
    3 account books.
  - Last Will and Testaments of Milly E. Falk and Henry Einstein, 1898-1947 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    Includes, among other documents, certified copy of Milly E. Falk's last will and testament; Estate of Milly E. Falk "B" Account checkbook; Myron Falk's Income Tax Record Book (income, deductions, securities) for 1918-1934; Falk's diary notes for August 6-September 17, 1945; and printed version of last will and testament of Henry L. Einstein.a letter to Myron Falk Jr.
  - U.S. Trust Company (1 of 2), 1927-1944 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
    Relates primarily to financial matters with the trusts set up under Henry Einstein's will for his grandchildren, Mildred and Myron Jr. Includes blueprint for West 53rd street (Falk owned building 44 W. 53rd).
  - U.S. Trust Company (2 of 2). Oversize, 1926-1944 (Box Oversize Small, Folder 2)
  - 126 East 70th Street documents, 1927-1946 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 19)
  - Insurance policies, 1940-1945 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
  - Financial and legal correspondence (2 folders), 1905-1944 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2-3)
    Includes, among other material, general financial correspondence, bills, tax related documents, Harmonie Club correspondence, Mercury Theatre/Orson Welles debt matters, photocopies of 1905 letters betwen Falk and William H. Burr on their joint interest in their published books, and legal documents regarding the trust of Henry L. Einstein.
  - Financial and legal correspondence (2 folders), 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4a-b)
    Includes, among other material, correspondence mentioning Orson Welles and the Mercury Theatre, WWII clippings and correspondence, bills, invoices, estimates, trust related documents, membership cards to clubs, and monthly statements for his properties.
  - Financial and legal correspondence (2 folders), 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5-6)
    Includes, among other material, stock certificates, bills, invoices, correspondence relating to World War II Ordnance department, taxes, insurance, trust accounts, and the Harmonie Club.
  - Myron Falk Estate Matters, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes letters to Myron Falk, Jr. regarding estate matters, including bequest to Mt. Sinai Hospital for endowment of a bed in the Chidren's Pavilion; letter regarding arrangements for sale of the Tophill Farm property; allocation of securities among trusts; and letter from the farm caretaker(?) regarding repairs, egg accounts and other matters. (Part of 2021 gift)
- Series IV. Print Matter, 1887-1932; 0.95 Linear feet
  This series contains a mixture of published material from 1889-1932, the bulk of which was authored by Myron S. Falk. There are three hardcover engineering books written by Falk, as well as the Second Annual State Water Commission report which includes Falk's individual report. There are also numerous copies of booklet reprints of Falk's engineering writings. Material not written by Falk include, among others, Union Prayer books, engineering textbooks, and two books inscribed to Henry L. Einstein and to Lewis Einstein.
  This series is arranged by format and then chronologically, beginning with the hardcover books authored by Falk, followed by the Second Annual Report of New York State Water Commission, the reprint booklets, and then books in the collection not authored by Falk.
  - Cements, Mortars, and Concretes by Myron S. Falk, 1904 (Offsite-box 4, Item 1)
    Inscribed to Henry Einstein
  - Design and Construction of Metallic Bridges by William H. Burr and Myron S. Falk, 1908 (Offsite-box 4, Item 2)
  - Influence Lines for Bridges and Roofs by William H. Burr and Myron S. Falk, 1909 (Offsite-box 4, Item 3)
  - Second Annual Report of the New York State Water Supply Commission, 1907 (Offsite-box 4, Item 4)
    Stamped with 'Myron S. Falk. Mar 5 - 1907.'
    Report of Myron S. Falk - Appendix I. Pages 24-69.
  - The Sanitary Disposal of Municipal Refuse. An Informal Discussion., 1903 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    By Messrs. Rudolph Hering, John McGaw Woodbury, H. De B. Parsons, W. F. Morse, George A. Soper, Theodore Horton, W. J. Baldwin, Charles B. Ball, M. N. Baker, Elmer W. Firth, Myron S. Falk, Charles H. Haswell, W. H. Booth, and H. A. Young.
    Reprinted from Transactions, Vol. L, page 95. (1903.)
  - Note on the Coefficient of Elasticity of Concrete and Mortar Beams During Flexure, 1903 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    Reprinted from Transactions, Vol. L, p. 473 (1903).
  - On the Use of Influence Lines in Graphic Statics, 1903 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    Reprinted from the School of Mines Quarterly, Vol. XXIV, January, No. 2, April, No.3, and July, No. 4, 1903.
  - The Detailed Design of a Railroad Bridge, 1904 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    By Wm. H. Burr and Myron S. Falk
    Reprinted from The School of Mines Quarterly Vol. XXV, April, 1904, No. 3, and July, 1904, No. 4
  - Some Primary Truss Principles, 1904-1905 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
  - Notes on The Design of High Masonry Dams, 1905 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
  - Influence Lines for Suspended Cantilevers, 1907 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from the School of Mines Quarterly, Vol. XXVIII, No. 3.
  - The Deflection Polygon of a Framed Structure as a Funicular Polygon, 1908 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from the School of Mines Quarterly, Vol. XXX, No. 1.
  - Displacement Diagrams of Framed Structures by Deflection Angles, 1908 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from the School of Mines Quarterly, Vol. XXIX, No. 3.
  - A System of Cost Keeping, 1909 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from Transactions, Vol. LXIV, p. 401 (1909).
  - Two Reinforced Concrete Coal Pockets, 1911 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from Transactions, Vol. LXXI, p. 192 (1911).
  - The Production of Toluol from Gas Plants, 1920 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    Reprinted from Transactions, Vol. LXXXIII, p. 904 (1920).
  - Copies of Falk booklet reprints (3 folders), 1903-1920 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9-11)
  - Engineering books, 1894-1932 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
    Books not written by Myron S. Falk.
    American Society of Civil Engineers: "Address at the Annual Convention, Hotel Wentworth, Near Portsmouth, N.H., June 21st, 1922." by John R Freeman; "Charges and Method of Making Charges for Professional Services" 1930
    "Notes on Code Words" by W.F. Friedman and C. J. Mendelsohn; inscription to Myron S. Falk by Charles J. Mendelsohn. 1932
    "Report of Board of Engineer Officers as to Maximum Span Practicable for Suspension Bridges" - Major Chas W. Raymond, Captain Wm. H. Bixby, Captain Edward Burr, Corps of Engineers, U.S. Army, Members of the Board. 1894
    "Notes on Foundations: Prepared for the Senior Class in Civil Engineering at Columbia University" By Wm. H. Burr
  - Le Siege de Berlin et Autres Contes par Alphonse Daudet, 1890 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    Was Lewis Einstein's copy of "The Siege of Berlin and Other Tales" by Alphonse Daudet. L. Einstein and drawings are written on the cover in pencil.
  - Poetical Works of John Godfrey Saxe, 1887 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 8)
    Inscribed "To Lewis Einstein from Columbia Grammar School for Excellence in English Composition, June 8, 1894." Cover (detached) embossed "Lewis Einstein."
  - Paris Universal Exposition. Civil Engineering, Public Works, and Architecture, 1889 (Offsite-box 5, Item 1)
    By William Watson
  - The Union Prayer Book for Jewish Worship Part I and II, 1895 (Offsite-box 5, Item 2)
    'Regine Wallach' written in ink on front page of Part 1; Myron S. Falk inscribed on Part II.
  - Program for the show "Uncle", 1897 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 9)
    Presented by the Columbia University sophomores, Class of 1899, as a benefit for '99 Freshman Crew team. (Part of 2021 gift)
  - Columbia University Commencement Programs, 1899, 1901, 1904 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
    Part of 2021 gift.
- Series V. Photographs and Drawings, circa 1870s-1950, undated; 3.74 Linear feet
  This series brings together photographs that were not found with other documents or related correspondence in the collection. They include personal photographs of Falk and his family, friends, and associates. There are also three photograph albums, one from 1903 in Yellowstone with captions, one likely from circa 1880s-90s relating to the Einstein family, and a third which could not be placed. Also included are oversize photos and drawings depicting a variety of subjects, such as dinners, a panorama of Myron Jr.'s Yale graduation, the Ordnance Department in Washington, D.C. during World War I, and Falk's parents. There is also a book of pictures of buildings with their addresses, built by H.H. Oddie Inc of which Falk was Chief Engineer.
  This series is arranged by subject matter, then chronologically.
  - American Silk Mission and other photographs (2 folders), Undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1-2)
    Includes photographs from two envelopes. One labeled "Japanese Trip" and other is a Kodak envelope. Includes a mix of photographs other than from American Silk Mission. Nitrate negatives from the Kodak packet were removed for separate storage.
  - Myron Falk headshots. Flat box, Undated (Offsite-box 6)
  - Arnold Falk (Myron's father as young man). Charcoal drawing. Oversize, 1879 (Offsite-box 15, Item 1)
    Item unframed and mounted by N-YHS conservator Alan Balicki, March 2021.
  - Kaufman Wallach (Myron's grandfather). Charcoal drawing. Oversize, 1879 (Offsite-box 15, Item 2)
  - Regine Wallach (Myron's grandmother). Charcoal drawing. Oversize, 1879 (Offsite-box 15, Item 3)
  - Myron S. Falk (as infant). Charcoal drawing. Oversize, 1879 (Offsite-box 17, Item 1)
    Signed "Falk." Item unframed and mounted by N-YHS conservator Alan Balicki, March 2021.
  - Arnold Falk (Myron's father as elderly man). Charcoal drawing. Oversize, undated (Offsite-box 16, Item 1)
    Item unframed and mounted by N-YHS conservator Alan Balicki, March 2021. Frame is also in box.
  - Family photographs, Undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tophill Farm / Thermix Corporation (1 of 2 folders), 1950, undated (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
    Includes 3 documents: 8x11 version of the oversize aerial view found in the following folder; a color photograph of the exterior of the main building, labeled "The House of Thermix," subsequent to its acquisition by the Thermix Corporation in 1950; and a marketing brochure of the company with images of the house, with cover letter to Falk, Jr., transmitting the brochure. (Photos in this folder and the next were part of 2021 gift.)
  - Tophill Farm / Thermix Corporation (2 of 2 folders) Oversize, undated (Box Oversize Small, Folder 3)
    Oversize aerial view of property and main building in Greenwich, Conn.
  - Photo albums (2 folders), Undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7-8)
    One album appears to be of a camping or hiking trip. The other album includes photos of ships, docks, a parade, storefronts, at least one view of the Columbian Exposition in Chicago, and other subjects. One nitrate negative was removed for separate storage.
  - Photo album, circa 1880s-1890s (Offsite-box 14, Folder 12)
    Photo album of cabinet cards, cartes-de-visite and tintypes. All are unidentified, however there are some photos of boys in baseball uniforms with the initials CGS, which is perhaps Columbia Grammar School, suggesting that these are photos of Lewis Einstein and the Einstein (Milly's) family.
  - Photo album of Yellowstone/Colorado Springs (2 folders), 1903 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5-6)
  - H. H. Oddie. Flat box (2 folders), 1919-1923 (Offsite-box 7)
    Includes pictures of the Kelly-Springfield Building (1919), N.Y. Telephone Building (167th St and Grand View Pl), Revillon Freres Building (1923). Examples of other photos include the Town Hall (concert hall), the Martin Beck Residence, The Cluny, 6th Municipal District Court, Ziegler Building, the State Bank (Madison Square Branch). The bulk of the photographs were taken by the Wurts Brothers or by H. Shobbrook Collins. There are also photographs of foundations built by Miller-Daybill & Co.
  - Dinner in honor of Shozabura Hoshino given by Mr. & Mrs. Eugene Atwood at the Hotel Astor. Oversize, 1925 January 14 (Drawer Oversize Large)
  - Society of American Magicians 22nd Annual Dinner at the Hotel McAlpin. Oversize, 1926 June 14 (Drawer Oversize Large)
  - Canoeing panorama. Oversize, Undated (Drawer Oversize Large)
    Thompson Photo Co. Rahway, NJ. n9 8011
  - Yale Graduation panorama. Oversize, 1928 (Drawer Oversize Large)
    Yale balloon in the middle
  - Ordnance Department, Washington, D.C. panorama. Oversize, 1919 January 3 (Drawer Oversize Large)
- Series VI. Artifacts, 1867-1945, undated; 3.17 Linear feet
  This series contains artifacts found throughout the collection, including diplomas and certificates from Columbia University, the War Department (World War II), and Congregation Emanu-El. The container list itemizes all artifacts.
  This series is arranged in chronological order with undated at the end.
  - Citizenship Naturalization Certificate, 1867 (Box Oversize Small, Folder 3)
    Certificate issued by the New York Court of Common Pleas granting U.S. citzenship to Arnold Falk (Myron Falk's father).
  - Napoleon III Emperor medal, 1869 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Einstein Family Bible, 5633 [1873] (Offsite-box 13, Item 1)
    Text translated to English by Isaac Leeser, Third Edition, Printed Philadelphia by Sherman & Co. for the Rev. Abraham De Sola. At back of book are three sheets of genealogical details (births, deaths, marriages), primarily for Milly Falk's parents, Henry L. Einstein (1849-1918) and Cecilia Sulzbacher (1855 or 1856-1943), and their immediate ancestors and two later generations.
  - World's Columbian Exposition medallion to Bound Brook Woolen Mills, 1892-1893 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Diploma for Lewis Einstein from Columbia Grammar School. Flat box, 1894 (Offsite-box 7)
  - Diploma from Columbia for Civil Engineering. Flat box, 1899 (Offsite-box 7)
  - Diploma from Stevens Institute of Technology. Oversize, 1900 (Box Oversize Small, Folder 3)
    Degree of Mechanical Engineer to Myron S. Falk.
  - Certificate/diploma granting Ph.D. to Myron Falk from Columbia. Oversize, 1904 (Box Oversize Small, Folder 3)
  - Two-handled cup, 1904? (Offsite-box 8)
    Small metal cup with two handles made of antlers(?), with inscription "To Myron S. Falk. With best wishes of Class of 1904, Civil Engineers, Columbia University." There is no maker's mark.
  - National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution. Membership Certificate. Oversize, 1914 (Box Oversize Small, Folder 3)
    Awarded to Milly Einstein Falk, national number 106998, given her descent from David Leivis, a soldier in the American Revolution.
  - Do Right and Fear No Man medal, 1916 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Merritt Haviland Smith medallion, 1926 (Offsite-box 8)
    Inscripted: "Engineer for 40 years of the Water Supply of the City of New York - Colonel of Artillery in the Great War 1862-1926"
  - Emanu-El donation receipt in honor of Arnold and Fannie Falk. Flat box, 1927 (Offsite-box 7)
  - World War II Commendation for Service. Flat box, 1945 (Offsite-box 7)
  - Wallet, Undated (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    Includes the business card and scrap papers found in Falk's wallet. One nitrate negative from the wallet was removed for separate storage.
  - Seal stamps (2), Undated (Offsite-box 8)
    Seal stamp 1 reads "Myron S. Falk Incorporated"; Seal stamp 2 reads "Myron S. Falk Chairman of Building Committee"
  - The "Aluminum" pocket seal with box, Undated (Offsite-box 8)
  - Thermometers (2). Flat box, Undated (Offsite-box 6)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Lines golf tees, Undated (Offsite-box 8)
  - Weaved paper, Undated (Offsite-box 8)
  - Coral, Undated (Offsite-box 8)
- Series VII. Film, 1920s-1950s; 4 Linear feet
  The series includes film taken mostly by Myron Falk in the 1920s-1930s. Falk's travels to the Middle East, Egypt, Europe, Panama, Brazil, Caribbean, and Western United States are included, but there do not appear to be any images from the American Silk Mission or other Asian travel. Falk's films also include images of home and family in Greenwich, Connecticut (commonly referred to in the collection as Port Chester, New York) and elsewhere. Some moving images were made by Myron Falk Jr. (Johnny), including European travel in the 1930s and later family images. Much of the film was digitized by the family and digital copies were included with the collection and in the series.
  During processing, the film was not viewed. Subject content noted in the container list was derived from the various labeling found on the reels and their canisters. Various labels appear to have been added over time and the container list notes their references, to the extent they could be read. All but a few reels included a reference number and a "new" number; both numbers are included in the container list.
  The series is arranged, with minor adjustment, as presented to N-YHS by the donor. Film related to "travel" opens the series and is found in boxes 9 and 10. These are followed by film related to "family" in boxes 11 and 12.
  Most of the reels were originally in four tin storage cases, labeled A-D. During processing at N-YHS, the film reels were rehoused into archival containers. The tin storage containers were discarded, however, the tins that housed the individual reels were retained as they have information written on them. Reels that were loose in the collection (i.e., not stored in one of the four tins) are also in Box 10. Digital media provided by the donor are noted at the close of the series.
  Access Restrictions
  The film reels are restricted from being viewed though the cans can be accessed for their information. The DVDs and USB with the digitized content provided by the donor are also restricted to avoid corruption of the original files. However, the contents were copied to N-YHS's network. For access to the files, contact manuscripts@nyhistory.org.
  - #21 / New #26 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can includes notes in Falk's handwriting, but cannot be fully made out: [2 words?] pictures of Scythian[?] trip. Modern tape on can: "Egypt."
  - #22 / New #27 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can is faded, but appears to refer to Luxor and other sites, 1923-1924. Original tape around can has notations: "Scythia trip", "Feb 23, 1927: Ferry up Nile River trip," "ED * FOU," and [Trip 2/24 Luxor?]. White leader on film marked as "Kids 1938 & 1939."
  - #23 / New #28 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can and similar to tape around can: "2/26/27: Nile, Luxor, Assuan, Kamomba [Kom Umbu?]." Modern tape on top of can: "Egypt."
  - #24 / New #29 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwritten note around can: "Scythia trip 1927, March." There are many other words; those that can be made out are: Jerusalem street scenes, Wailing Wall, Palestine, Bethlehem. Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Jerusalem, Egypt." Tape on reel: "Herbert [name?] Scythia trip, Feb-Apr 1927."
  - #25 / New #30 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Mixture, Jerusalem, Venice." Modern tape: "Jerusalem."
  - #26 / New #31 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on tape around can: "Feb 1927: Constantinople, the Mosques[?], American College, Stadium, Acropolis, The Scythia [word?], Venice, St. Marks." White leader on reel marked: Panama 1932.
  - #27 / New #32 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can is too faded to read, but dates from March 14-22. Modern tape: Munich 192?
  - #28 / New #33 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwritten note around can: "Scythia trip, March 1927: Rhine [Bemberg?] Factory [several unidentified words], Amsterdam, [Brussels?], Paris Races, [Alice Cocher?]." Original handwritten on bottom of can: [?] 3/26, Amsterdam 3/28, Brussels 3/31, Paris Apr 1-[4?]." Modern tape: Amsterdam, Brussels, Paris."
  - #30 / New #34 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Colored [word?], Pictures Panama, 1929 [1927 also appears]." Modern tape: "Panama 1927. Myron, Eleanor, Mildred "boy dancing" good. rest is boring." "Reviewed by Mike & Lynne, 12/3/12."
  - #37 / New #37 (Offsite-box 9, Reel -)
    Written on bottom of can: "Montego Bay, 1934" and "Rapps, Pursells, Hoggs."
  - #36 / New #39 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    Handwritten on bottom of can: "Panama, Feb 1933. [word?] Caracas, [word?], Panama." Modern tape on can and on reel: "Panama 1933, ?, Caracas, Caracas, Panama. Myron Falk, Cruise."
  - #35 / New #40 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    No can. Modern plastic reel. Tape on reel: "1932: Panama, Havana [3 words]."
  - #39 / New #41 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Scythia, #1 Pier, 4 Madeira, Granada." Original tape around can: "Roma, Feb 1937." Modern tape: "SS Romo '37, Medit"
  - #34 / New #43 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Mexico City, Ribera, Cuernavaca, Buckingham Palace, [Berongaria?] Howes, Bemberg Pl."
  - #33 / New #44 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Mexico, Apr 20/31."
  - #38 / New #45 (Offsite-box 10, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: 1936: Auto trip #2, Grand Canyon [other words unclear, including Patricia?]"
  - #5 / New #2 (Offsite-box 11, Reel -)
    Original handwriting on bottom of can: "Duck hunting, football, Pre-28." Original tape around is difficult to read, but seems to include: [Yale West Point football?], Duck hunting, Naumberg, Bemberg officials, Godwin, Eleanor, Our house. Modern tape: "1925: Picnic, Duck hunting, aereal views of Portchester." On white leader of film: 1925: "Duck hunt/aereal."
  - #4 / New #3 (Offsite-box 11, Reel -)
    Original handwritten on bottom of can: "Bucklands, Yale Game, Portchester scenes, 1925." Original tape around can is difficult to read but seems to include the following words, among many others: Portchester, father, Johnny on horse, Yale, Bucklands. Modern tape: 1925: "Family, football game, Portchester." On white leader of film: "Family 1925."